

CONTACT ME

Phone +84938925905

Email nguyenkhoi2412@gmai

l.com

Address 391TK 42/45 Tran Hung

Dao, Cau Kho Ward, District 1, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

BASIC INFORMATION

Birthday 06/01/1983
Nationality Vietnamese
Marital Status Married
Gender Male

SKILLS

- Front End
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- HTML
- CSS
- Css Responsive Design
- HTML5
- MVC
- ASP.NET
- ReactJS
- Ant Design

LANGUAGES

English

KHOI NGUYEN LE MINH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - 10 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE

ABOUT ME

I graduated from University of Technology and study in higher diploma in software engineering. I have over 10 years experience in web application development, especially in frontend web development. I develop HTML / CSS / and javascript coding, making the site responsive and friendlier to smaller devices is one of my main aims as well as improving performance. Through the professional knowledge I have and with my experience, I will try to do the best job at the company. Constantly strive for yourself and become the core employee of the company in the coming time.

EDUCATION

09/2001 - 08/2004: Expert programming

Others - Aptech Scrool

Higher diploma in software engineering

09/2001 - 08/2004: Information Technology

College - University of Technology

WORK HISTORY

01/2022 - Current: .NET Developer

Stepmedia Software Viet Nam

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET CORE, C#...
- Frontend is using REACTJS, SASS...
- Company product development Deloitte, write new features reports, improve performance for APIs, troubleshooting to perfect products...

01/2018 - 09/2020: Frontend Developer

CONEXUS VIET NAM

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5... And my specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css...
- Programming vip24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project is a learning experience which aims to provide students with the opportunity to synthesise knowledge from various areas of learning, and critically and creatively apply it to real life situations. This process, which enhances students' knowledge and enables them to acquire skills like collaboration, communication and independent learning, prepares them for lifelong learning and the challenges ahead.

11/2012 - 01/2018: Frontend Developer

Orient Software Development Corp.

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5... And my specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css...
- Programming vip24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project. Planner create course & learner join courses to study...

06/2011 - 11/2012: Developer

VIEN NAM SOFTWARE

- Programing projects websites for clients.
- Analysis, programming and development website application on the basic platform .NET 2.0, 3.5, 4.0... using ASP.NET, MVC, Entity Framework, Web services, html, jquery, css...

01/2008 - 01/2010: Technical support

FPT TELECOM

- Support clients about ADSL, LAN, WAN. Check client's connection on system, check information and all services assigned to clients.
- Support all problems that IT need to solve about Web server, mail server, FTP, IP static, NAT and troubleshoot IT's problems.
- Configure router.

CERTIFICATIONS

2004: University Of Technology

Software Engineering

2004: FPT Aptech

Software Engineering